as we go to our next game the fighters
Club Roast the fighters Club
Roast since Star Wars the Force of
wagens was announced did I mention that
I'm going to the premere tonight I'm
going I'm so excited came contain myself
I want I can't shut up Chris Hardwick uh
this has been dominating the
conversations online there are even Star
Wars grapes Star Wars grapes for when
you want to pretend you're eating Yoda's
balls
Star Wars grapes eat my balls you
[Laughter]
will
now I'm as excited as the next ner I'm
beyond excited about this movie but I do
think Star Wars could stand to be taken
down a peg right so we're right I don't
agree with that either but for the
purposes of this bit we're doing an
Intergalactic row so I have to say that
comedians I'm going to give you each a
set of Star Wars characters from the
Star Wars wiki Wikipedia uh and for 250
points you're going to roast their goofy
mugs Jesse your first roast victim is
Chewbacca Chewbacca Chewbacca you look
like a Sasquatch and you live in a
spaceship you're like a redneck
unicorn there must be a line around the
block of hicks trying to get Fu in the
ass by
you I don't know how I feel about that
with the sweater
[Applause]
uh
sure next up Ponda Baba p
Baba are are you choking on a
[Laughter]
Kardashian you're the only you're the
only Star Wars character who gets his
teeth cleaned at the
gynecologist oh well played well played
cou you have
Yoda Yoda oh my God he's so adorable and
ugly at the same time it's like if Mr
Miyagi and ET had sex that's what Yoda
would be
which one got
pregnant next up Admiral abbar Admiral
abbar Admiral abbar Way to make every
spaceship smell like
fish yeah he gets you in there and then
it's a
trap Al first up from the force awakens
kylo Ren oh kylo what's up man you're a
newcomer bro yeah people don't know much
about you I like your name kylo Ren
you're the only villain that seems like
you were named by a Hollywood super
couple your name's Kyle no it's kylo
kill yourself yeah I mean we don't know
much about you except that you're black
which is really all anybody knows about
me in this
[Laughter]
audience keeping moving next up Wicket
oh oh a Chris what are you doing I can't
make fun of something that's cute he's
adorable he's a Savage he' eat you had
the
chance that's what they are you know
look hey look I like no matter what they
say I like you you know and uh we'll
still be friends even though you don't
fall for the uh peanut butter trick like
my dog
does at least not
[Applause]
yet